offersclick.co.uk 2013-01-18

# Offers Click - Privacy Policy

The following sites are direct marketing trade and domain names of Acxiom Limited ("Acxiom"), a UK company, which integrates data, services and technology to create and deliver customer and information management solutions for many of the largest, most respected companies in the world:

Included sites:  

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not use or share the information you give without your consent, which is given when you provide information via the on-line registration forms on our site.

## Use of your data

Your answers will be protected by the Data Protection Act 1998 and controlled by Acxiom. Acxiom will use your information for developing products & services, marketing, research, & updating and correcting databases. Acxiom may pass this information to other reputable organisations, which may use it for those purposes too. Acxiom and these reputable organizations may contact you by mail, email, telephone, SMS, using cookies and in other ways, with details of their products and services and for other legitimate business reasons. By providing information at any of our sites you consent to your information being used in all of the above ways.

Certain questions have been included in the survey on behalf of:  

  * All Response Media
  * Bauer Media
  * Cida Investments
  * Club la Costa
  * Crystal Windows
  * Dennis Publishing
  * E-On
  * Eurodebt
  * Golden Charter
  * Grove Financial
  * Hearst Magazines
  * Hilite
  * Honda
  * Just Eat Group
  * LGS Limited
  * Marketing Craze
  * Medialab
  * Mitchell Farrar
  * RAPP Ltd
  * Research Now
  * Response One
  * Roberts Jackson Ltd
  * Scottish Power 
  * Talk Talk
  * TNS UK Ltd
  * Worldwide Wealth Collections

## Unsubscribing

You can unsubscribe from further emails via a link in any of the emails you receive. You can also unsubscribe from the service at any time by clicking [here](http://www.offersclick.co.uk/SiteRender.aspx?SiteID=540&ThemeID=2) or by sending an email to [UKConsumerServices@Acxiom.com](mailto:UKConsumerServices@Acxiom.com) with the subject line "Unsubscribe", or by writing to:

Acxiom Limited  
17 Hatfields,  
London,  
SE1 8DJ or by ringing 020 7526 5139 (UK office hours only). 

## Cookie Policy

Your information may be used to place small text files (known as 'cookies') on your device. Cookies are used for different purposes as set out below but overall to improve your user experience across our sites and the relevance of adverts that are served to you. Cookies are a commonplace tool used by all major websites.

_Functional cookies:_  
Our functional cookies are only used by Acxiom to improve your user experience. They enable us to recognise you when you return to one of our websites and save you having to fill out the registration form each time you visit. These cookies will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your name and address) that you have not otherwise given to us. The information collected using these cookies cannot track your browsing activity on other web sites. The cookies make our websites easier and more rewarding for you.

_Website performance cookies:_  
Acxiom uses website performance cookies (via Google Analytics; click [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html) to review their Privacy Policy) to analyse traffic information such as the pages you visit, the time you spend on the site. These cookies are anonymous and we do not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. The information collected using these cookies cannot track your browsing activity on other web sites. 

Acxiom also uses tracking pixels to measure visits to the site from one particular source (e.g. a specific banner or email campaign) and the response rates from these sources. These tracking pixels will not collect your browsing history and are used for website and traffic source performance purposes only.

_Targeting cookies:_   
Acxiom and its partners may use your information to place targeting cookies on to your device. These cookies are used to share your browsing history with third parties (advertisers or social networks) to make adverts more relevant to you. By allowing these cookies, you are more likely to get relevant adverts while you visit other sites. Preventing these cookies will not stop adverts but they will be less tailored to your interests. Currently, Acxiom allows one organisation, called [exelate](http://exelate.com/consumer-opt-out/services-privacy-policy/), to place targeting cookies. You can choose not to have these cookies placed on your device by clicking [here](http://exelate.com/consumer-opt-out/) .

**Your consent**  
By providing information at any of our sites, you agree to the terms of this cookie policy. However at any time, you can choose to disable our cookies by changing your browser settings. If you do not agree to this cookie policy, please do not use our sites.

## Security Policy

The importance of security for your personally identifiable information is of utmost concern to us. We have systems in place to assist us in providing secure transmission of your information from your device to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Acxiom does not warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. By using this site, you signify your agreement to this security policy. If you do not agree to it, please do not use this site. 

## Complaints Procedure

A complaint may be registered using any of the contact points listed in this Privacy Policy. We will acknowledge your complaint within 5 working days and respond in full within 20 working days. If you are unhappy with our response to your complaint you have the right to escalate the matter to our industry self-regulator the Direct Marketing Commission.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2012_

Acxiom Limited  
17 Hatfields,  
London,  
SE1 8DJ
